老爸让我们继续他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off…
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
saving people, hunting things, the family business.
- 你还在用信用卡欺诈吗？- 你以为干这事容易？
- Still running credit-card scams? - Think credit card fraud's easy?
好的 马科维茨先生
Okay, Mr.Burkowitz.
- 联邦执法官 - 环境研究专业的
- Federal marshals. - Environmental majors.
我是西蒙斯神父 美国野生动植物管理处的
Father Simmons.U.S.Wildlife Service.
- 奈吉尔·塔夫内尔 - 杰瑞·卡普兰医生
- Nigel Tuffnel. - Dr.Jerry Kaplan.
- 我们是记者 - 警察
- Reporters. - Art dealers.
社区兄弟 国家安全局？
Students.Homeland Security.
对我们来说这是违法的
Pretty illegal, even for us.
特警队发现了一名当地女性被绑架 而且还被封口
SWAT team discovered a local woman bound and gagged.
袭击者是一名24到30岁的男性白人
Her attacker, a white male, approximately 24 to 30 years of age…
而且当场被抓
was discovered hiding in the home.
- 变形人？- 每个文化中都有变形人的传说
- Shapeshifter? - Every culture has a shapeshifter lore.
可以将自己变成任何动物或人形
Legends of creatures who can transform themselves into animals or other men.
嘿
Hey.
警察认为艾米丽
Cops are blaming this Dean Winchester guy…
是被迪恩·温彻斯特杀害的
for Emily's murder.
- 对不起 我可能会想念这个 - 想念什么？
- Sorry I'm gonna miss it. - What?
我到底有多少次机会 能看到我自己的葬礼？
How many chances will I have to see my own funeral?
（马里兰州 巴尔的摩）
用这个名字？
Under what name?
是的 那是我最喜欢的
Oh, yeah, that's my favorite so far.
三个州可能用的ID我们已经知道了
Possible IDs in three states that we know of.
我再打给你
I gotta call you back.
好…
Well…
首先 我还以为你只是个新手
first I thought you were just stepping up your game.
信用卡欺诈
Credit card fraud…
非法进入 这个有点让人不解
breaking and entering.Now, this one puzzled me.
挖坟
Grave desecration.
但这些都比不上杀人
But still, these are a long way from murder.
圣路易丝有传真给我们…
Then we get a fax from St.Louis.
你在那里被怀疑 虐待和杀害一名年轻女性
Where you're suspected of torturing and murdering a young woman.
然而 没人能证明这一切
However, no one could prove anything, of course…
因为你在那里假死
because, supposedly, you died there.
- 双手放在我可以看见的地方 - 但我想告诉你一些事…
Hands where I can see them. - But I gotta tell you something.
你看上去还很健壮
You look pretty healthy to me.
我知道 凯伦·吉尔斯并不是你杀的第一个人
So now we know Karen Giles wasn't the first person you murdered.
想逃吗 萨姆？
Going somewhere, Sam?
但我可以保证 她将会是最后一个受害者
But I guarantee you, she's the last.
[邪恶力量 第2季第7集]
我想你也许口渴了
Thought you might be thirsty.
你是个好警察
Okay, so you're the good cop.
- 那个坏警察呢？- 和你老哥在一起
- Where's the bad cop? - He's with your brother.
你还留我们这在里做什么？
Okay.And you're holding us why?
他现在是杀人嫌疑犯
He's being held on suspicion of murder.
- 你呢？我们要看着办了 - 杀人犯？
- And you? We'll see. - Murder?
听声音感觉你真的很惊讶 要么你就是个不错的演员？
You sound genuinely surprised.Or are you that good of an actor?
- 他到底杀了谁了？- 我们会查出来的
- Who's he supposed to have murdered? - We'll get to that.
没有正式被起诉之前你不能扣留我们
You can't just hold us here without charges.
事实上 我们可以扣留你们48小时
Well, actually, we can for 48 hours.
你是前法律系学生 你知道这条规定
But you, being a prelaw student, would know that.
我对你很了解 萨姆
I know all about you, Sam.
你23岁 没工作 没家庭住址
You're 23 years old, no job, no home address.
在婴儿时你妈就死了
Your mother died when you were a baby.
你父亲下落不明
Your father's whereabouts are unknown.
而且你老哥迪恩有案子在身
And then there's the case of your brother, Dean.
他的死真有点夸张
Whose demise was, well, just a little bit exaggerated.
你们好像过得很随心所欲
Feel free to jump in whenever you like.
不好意思了？没问题 我会继续的
Shy? No problem, I'll keep going.
在你儿时你家搬过很多次
Your family moved around a lot when you were a kid.
除此之外 你还是个A等生
Despite that, you were a straight A student.
拿全年奖学金进入斯坦福德大学
Got into Stanford with a full ride.
但在一年前 你的公寓着了一场火
Then, about a year ago, there was a fire in your apartment.
烧死了 杰西卡·穆尔 你的女朋友
One fatality, Jessica Moore, your girlfriend.
在她死后 你就不见踪影
After she died, you fell off the grid.
放弃了一切
Left behind everything.
我需要时间来…
I needed some time off.
养伤
To deal.
所以我和我老哥一起公路旅行
So I'm taking a road trip with my brother.
感觉怎么样？
How's that going for you?
很好
Great.
我意思是…
I mean…
我们看到了美国大陆上的第二大绒线球
we saw the second largest ball of twine in the continental U.S.
很棒
Awesome.
我们在档案库里找到了迪恩的指纹
We ran Dean's fingerprints through AFIS.
- 好 - 而且可能有几十个
- Okay. - Got over a dozen possible hits.
「可能」的指纹 那就没有什么意义
Possible hits.Which makes them worthless.
但你想想 如果我们也找到了你的指纹呢？
But makes you wonder.What are we gonna find when we run your prints?
是的 嗯… 你会让我知道的 不是吗？
Yeah.Well, you be sure to let me know, all right?
我能喝吗？
May I?
- 请吧 - 太好了
- Please. - Great.
萨姆 你是个好孩子
Sam, you seem like a good kid.
迪恩当你的哥哥不是你的错
It's not your fault Dean's your brother.
我们不能选择我们的出身
We can't pick our family.
现在圣路易丝的侦探在挖坟
Right now, detectives in St.Louis are exhuming a corpse.
他们试着找出 在虐待了那么多妇女之后
They're trying to figure out how your brother faked his own death…
你哥是如何玩假死把戏的
after torturing all those young women.
迪恩不是个好人
Dean's a bad guy.
他的生活已经结束
His life is over.
但你的生活没有
Yours doesn't have to be.
你想让我指证我老哥？
You want me to turn against my own brother?
不是 我们在凯伦·吉尔斯的被害现场
No.We already caught him cold.
抓住这个冷血 双手沾满血的家伙
Red handed at the Karen Giles murder scene.
我们只是需要你… 说出我们不知道的片断
We just need you to fill in some missing pieces.
我为什么要那么做？
Why would I do that?
因为我可以向检查官求情
Because I can talk to the DA.
和你做个交易
Make a deal for you.
你可以继续你的生活
You can get on with your life.
迪恩就让他沉沦吧
Dean's as good as gone.
我父亲和托尼·吉尔斯是老朋友
My dad and Tony Giles were old friends.
他们一直在一起工作
They were in the service together.
你知道 我们在孩童时代就认识他了
We've known him since we were kids, you know.
所以在听到他的死讯就马上赶过去了
We came when we heard about his death.
这给你
There you go.
- 安东尼·吉尔斯 - 谁是安东尼·吉尔斯？
- Anthony Giles. - Who's Anthony Giles?
巴尔的摩的一个律师
A Baltimore lawyer.
在办公室工作很晚 你可以看看
Working late at his office.Check it out.
他的喉咙被割断了 但他的房间却很干净
His throat was slit, but the room was clean.
- 没有DNA 没有指纹 - 看下去 会好的
- No DNA, no prints. - Keep reading.It gets better.
保安录相带没有拍到攻击者
"Security cameras failed to capture footage of the assailant."
- 或者有人拿走了录相带 - 要么他就是隐形杀手
- Somebody tampered with the tapes. - Or it's an invisible killer.
我种喜欢这种案子了
My favorite kind.
- 你有什么想法 斯卡利？- 我不是斯卡利 你才是斯卡利
- What you think, Scully? Check it out? - I'm not Scully.You're Scully.
不 我是马尔德 你是那个红发女人
No, I'm Mulder.You're a redheaded woman.
所以…
So…
你们没有足够证据证明迪恩杀了托尼
would've been hard for Dean to kill Tony…
- 因为那个时候不在城里 - 那告诉我接着发生了什么？
- …considering we weren't in town. - Tell me what happened next.
好 嗯 所以我们去看了凯伦
Okay, that's when we went to see Karen.
她可能认不出我们了
She was barely holding it together.
我们只是想去那里安慰下她
We just wanted to be there for her, you know.
保险
Insurance.
我已经忘记保险的事了
I totally forgot about the insurance.
打扰你我们感到很抱歉
We're very sorry to bother you right now…
但保险公司还是需要做点调查的
but the company is required to conduct its own investigation.
- 你明白的吧？- 是的
- You understand? - Sure.
你能告诉我们
Okay.If you could just tell us anything…
有关你丈夫死那晚的一些情况吗？
you remember about the night your husband died.
我和托尼准备一起吃晚餐
Tony and I were supposed to have dinner.
他打电话说他电脑有问题
He called and said that he was having computer troubles…
所以要加班
and he had to work late.
就是这样
That was it.
你认为他会有什么仇人会这么做
You have any idea who could have done this?
不 不 就像我对警察说的那样 我 我不知道
No.No.It's like I told the police, I have no idea.
托尼有提到一些不寻常的事吗？
Did Tony mention anything unusual…
在他死前的那几天？
to you in the days before his death?
不寻常？
Unusual?
是的 就是很奇怪的事
Yeah, like strange.
- 奇怪 - 凯伦 很古怪的事
- Strange? - You know, Karen, weird.
古怪的声音
Weird noises…
影像 诸如此类
visions, anything like that?
- 嗯 - 什么
- Ahem. - What?
在他死前他做了个噩梦
He had a nightmare the day before he died, but
什么样的噩梦？
What kind of a nightmare?
在半夜的时候他醒过来了
He said that he woke up in the middle of the night.
有一个女人坐在他的床边
There was a woman standing at the foot of the bed.
他眼前一片空白 接着她就走了
He blinked, she was gone.
我意思是 那只是个恶梦而已
I mean, it was just a nightmare.
他有没有说她长的什么样
Did he say what she looked like?
她的长相有那么重要吗？
What the hell difference does it make what she looked like?
我们的公司要调查的很彻底
It's just our company's very thorough.
他说她很苍白 她有黑色和红色的眼睛
He said she was pale and she had dark red eyes.
所以我抱了下凯伦
So I gave Karen a hug.
告诉她如果需要帮助就打电话给我 就是这样
Told her to call me if she needed anything, and that was it.
结束了
End of story.
萨姆 我想帮你的
Sam, I am trying to help you here.
但你要对我坦白
But you have got to be honest with me.
我有目击证人
Now, we have an eyewitness.
看见二个男人
Someone who saw two men…
身形和你俩一样的人闯入吉尔斯办公室
fitting your and your brother's description breaking into Giles'office.
听着 凯伦随后打电话给我们
Look, Karen called us later, said there was stuff she wanted…
她想从托尼的办公室拿点东西 但警察不让她进去
from Tony's office, but the police weren't letting her in.
就拿一张他们在巴黎的照片 还有些其它东西
Like a picture of the two of them in Paris, and some other stuff.
听着 进入犯罪现场是不对的行为 但是她给我们的钥匙
Look, it was wrong to enter a crime scene, but she gave us the key.
嘿
Hey.
吉尔斯尸体就是在那儿被发现的
Anthony Giles'body was found right about here.
喉咙口的切痕很深 都可以看到脊梁骨了
"Throat slit so deep, part of his spinal cord was visible."
你怎么看？
What do you think?
复仇恶灵？邪恶的复仇？
Vengeful spirit, underline vengeful?
有可能
Yeah, maybe.
他看见了个女人坐在他的床头
I mean, he did see that woman at the foot of his bed.
看看这个
Hey, look at this.
Dana Shulps？
那是什么 是名字？
What's that? A name?
我不知道 但到处都是
I don't know, but it's everywhere.
只工作 不玩耍 聪明小孩也变傻
All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy.
我想这事已经可以归入怪事之列了
Wow.
I'd say we've officially crossed over into weird.
吉尔斯可能认识那恶灵
Maybe Giles knew her.
有可能是那白脸红眼神秘女孩的名字
Maybe it's the name of our pale, red eyed mystery girl.
让我们看看
Well, let's see what we can see.
找不出Dana和Shulps这两个词的意思
There's not a single mention of a Dana Shulps anywhere.
没有Shulpsor
There's not a D.Shulps…
- 或Shulps这样的词 - 好极了
- …or any other kind of frigging Shulps. - Great.
- 你找到什么？- 没有
- What do you got? - Nothing.
至少在过去50年内
No Dana Shulps has ever lived or died in Baltimore…
- 巴尔的摩没有叫Dana Shulps的人 - 那现在怎么办？
- …in the last 50 years, at least. - So, what now?
我想我快要破解吉尔斯电脑里的密码了
Well, I think I'm pretty close to cracking Giles'password.
- 有可能这里面会有些发现 - 「快」是多久…
- Maybe something in his personal files. - By close you mean…?
大概30分钟
Thirty minutes maybe.
太好了
Awesome.
那我还是出去晃晃
So I guess I just get to hang out.
好主意
So awesome.
- 伙计 - 你搞什么
- Dude, seriously. - All right.
我要和凯伦再谈一次
I'm gonna talk to Karen
问问她是不是认识Dana Shulps这个人？
see if she knows anything about this Dana Shulps.
好的
Great.
接着用功吧
Keep going, sparky.
接着迪恩就回到了凯伦的住处看一看
Dean went back to Karen's place to check up on her.
我意思 你知道的 我先前很不安的样子
I mean, you know, she'd been pretty upset earlier.
那你为什么不和他一起去？
So why didn't you go with him?
我直接回了汽车旅馆
I just went back to the motel.
顺便问一下 你怎么知道我在那儿的？
How'd you know I was there, by the way?
在逮捕你哥哥时 发现了那些汽车旅馆小册子
We found the motel matchbook on your brother when we arrested him.
不要再兜圈子了 在巴尔的摩你一直和你哥哥在一起
Let's quit fooling around.You were with your brother the whole time…
现在为什么没在一起？
you were in Baltimore.Why separate now?
- 因为你哥哥撇下你之后 去杀凯伦了 - 他没杀人
- Your brother left to go murder Karen. - He didn't kill anyone.
我听到911的电话
I heard the 911 call.
凯伦很害怕
Karen was terrified.
她说有人在她家里
She said someone was in the house.
- 紧急事件服务中心 - 有人吗？
- Emergency services. - Hello.
- 我看到有陌生人在我家里 - 你的住址 女士？
- I think I saw somebody in my house. - What is your address?
克林顿大街421号
It's 421 Clinton Avenue.
- 请你们 - 哈喽？
- Please, can you? Hello?
凯伦 你在吗？
Karen, you in there?
喔 上帝啊
Oh, God.
真是的 这到底是什么？
Seriously, what the hell?
别动 别动
Freeze.Stay on your knees.
把手举起来
Hands where I can see them.
现在
Now.
拷住他
Cuff him.
- 你一直盯着他？- 没有
- You getting anywhere with him? - No.
只是听他说些鬼话
Just a lot of wise ass remarks.
你呢？
You?
萨姆说的和昨天迪恩交待的相附
Sam's story matches Dean's to the last detail.
是的 这两个家伙真有默契 我要让他们好看
Yeah? Well, these guys are good, I'll give them that.
如果萨姆不肯说
If we don't get Sam to flip, we have nothing…
我们除了环境证据外就没有其它证据了
but a lot of circumstantial evidence.
我们在犯罪现场逮到迪恩的
We got Dean at the crime scene…
当时他手上还有血呢
with blood on his hands.
陪审团至少会采纳一下
Juries have convicted for less.
是的 但杀人凶器在拿呢？
Yeah, but, I mean, where's the murder weapon?
动机是什么？你说过要有合理的怀疑
What's the motive? You talk about reasonable doubt
戴安娜…
Diana…
你能提出合理怀疑吗？
do you have reasonable doubt?
我们要时刻关注这两人个 其中一个必是突破口
We keep leaning on these guys, one of them will tumble.
不要忘记圣路易丝的事
And don't forget about St.Louis.
我跟你说 迪恩就是我们要找的人
I'm telling you, this Dean guy is our guy.
我知道 托尼·吉尔斯是你的朋友
I know Tony Giles was a friend of yours.
是的 他是的 而且是好朋友
Yeah, he was.He was a good friend.
我知道你想快点了结这个案子
Look, and I know you wanna clean this mess up quick.
得了吧 托尼知道很多犯罪类型 也许我们
But come on, Tony knew a lot of criminal types, maybe we just
犯罪类型？
Criminal types?
但他是一个辩护律师
He was a defense lawyer for God's sakes.
他当然知道犯罪类型
Of course he knew criminal types.
那好 我们再去问问他俩
Okay.All right, let's get back at them.
让他们好好想想吧
No.You know what?
Let them stew in their juices for a bit.
到这边来
Come here.
Dana Shulps Dana Shulps
Dana…Dana Shulps
这有可能不是人名 这有可能不是人名
Maybe it's not a name.Maybe it's not a name.
错位构词吗？
Anagram maybe?
- 温彻斯特先生吗？- 是的
- Mr.Winchester? - Yeah.
我是杰夫·克劳斯
I'm Jeff Krause.
我是公共辩护团的
I'm with the public defender's office.
我是你的律师
I'm your lawyer.
喔 感谢上帝 我有救了
Oh, thank God, I'm saved.
能借我笔和纸吗？
Hey, can I steal a pen from you, some paper?
当然可以
Sure.
警察还没发现凶器 那样很好
Well, the police haven't found a weapon yet, so that's good.
可他们发现了你的指纹
But they got your prints…
你手上的鲜血
and, literally, blood on your hands.
加上你在警局的记录
And with your police record…
温彻斯特先生？你在干什么？
Mr.Winchester, what are you doing?
- 我觉得这里用的是错位构词 - 什么？
- I think it's an anagram. - A what?
错位构词 同样的字母 排列成不同的单词
An anagram.Same letters, different words.
你能不能帮我个忙？
Could you do me a favor?
看能不能认出这几个词
See if you recognize any of these words.
本地的人名 地名 诸如此类的东西
Local names, places, anything like that?
你知不知道这些指控有多严重？
Do you understand how serious these charges are?
我正铐在张桌子上 是的 我有数
I'm handcuffed to a table.Yeah, I get it.
就当满足我一下 看一眼
Humor me.Take a quick look.
哦
Well…
S- U- P？不是很清楚 不过…
S-U-P, I don't know about that…
阿什兰是一条街的名字
but Ashland is a street name.
- 离这里不远 - 街名？
- It's not far from here. - Street?
那么先告诉我 托尼·吉尔斯死的那天晚上你在哪？
Let's start with where you were the night that Anthony Giles died.
- 你能见到我弟弟吗？- 温彻斯特先生…
- Can you get in to see my brother? - Mr.Winchester…
你有可能被判死刑
you could be facing a death penalty here.
谢谢你的法律咨询 马特洛克先生
Hey, thanks for the law review, Matlock.
可如果你真想帮我…
But if you wanna help me…
就请你去见我弟弟
I need you to see my brother.
我希望那对你有用
I hope that was meaningful.
可我现在想讨论一下你的案子
But I'd like to discuss your case now.
没问题 马特洛克
Sure thing, Matlock.
你俩真不愧是亲兄弟？
You two really are brothers, aren't you?
现在… 如你所知
Now, as you know…
地方法官可能会打算要…
the DA might be interested in
我们需要你去陪同另一位
We need you.With the other one.
律师先生
Counselor…
你的当事人决定要招供了
your boy decided to confess.
温彻斯特先生 我强烈建议你不要这样做
Mr.Winchester, I'd advise against that strongly.
对着摄像头说
Talk directly into the camera.
先说说你叫什么名字
Start by stating your name for the record.
我叫迪恩·温彻斯特
My name is Dean Winchester.
我是水瓶座 我喜欢看日落
I'm an Aquarius.I enjoy sunsets…
喜欢打着赤脚走在沙滩上 还喜欢火辣的女人
long walks on the beach, and frisky women.
我没有杀人 可我知道是谁干的…
And I did not kill anyone.But I know who did.
或者说什么东西干的更确切
Or rather, what did.
当然 我还不能十分肯定
Of course, it can't be for sure
因为我在调查的时候被抓住了
because our investigation was interrupted.
但是我们的想法是 我们要找的是一个
Our working theory is that we're looking for a kind of…
复仇的幽灵
vengeful spirit.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你知道 鬼马小精灵的嗜血杀手版
You know, Casper the bloodthirsty ghost?
托尼·吉尔斯看见过
Tony Giles saw it.
我打赌那个凯伦女孩也见过
I'll bet you cash money Karen did too.
知道吗 有趣的是它留下的字
The interesting thing is the word it leaves behind.
出于某些原因 它试图告诉我们些什么
For some reason, it's trying to tell us something.
可是和这个世界沟通并不容易
But communicating across the veil aingt easy.
有时候这些幽灵会把事情弄糟
Sometimes the spirits, they get things jumbled.
你们听过Redrum（反过来是谋杀Murder）吧 那是一样的
You remember redrum? Same concept.
它可能是断字
You know, it's…Could be word fragments.
其他时候…
Other times…
可能是被打乱的单词
it's anagrams.
起初我们猜想 那是一个名字Dana Suhulps
See, at first we thought this was a name, Dana Shulps.
但现在我们觉得那是条街道 阿什兰大街
But now, we think it's a street.Ashland.
不管是什么
Whatever's going on…
- 我猜想那里就是源头 - 你这个傲慢的混蛋
- …I'm betting it started there. - You arrogant bastard.
托尼和凯伦都是正派人 你却在拿他们开玩笑
Tony and Karen were good people.You're making jokes.
我没开玩笑 蠢货
I'm not joking, Ponch.
你冷血地谋杀了他们 就象你杀那个圣路易斯的女孩一样
You murdered them in cold blood just like that girl in St.Louis.
噢 对了 那也不是我干的
Oh, yeah, that wasn't me either.
是那个变成我模样的变形人干的
That was a shapeshifter creature that only looked like me.
起来 嘿 嘿
Get up.Hey, hey.
皮特 放手
Pete, that is enough.
是你要我说实话的
You asked for the truth.
别让他跑了
Lock his ass up.
怎么回事？
What the hell?
他人呢？
Where is he?
他是怎样做到的？
What'd he do?
消防梯离的那么远。-。-
The fire escape's way over
- 什么？- 这两家伙
- What? - These two guys.
希尔茨和麦奎因？什么意思
Hilts and McQueen? What is that?
希尔茨是斯蒂夫·麦奎因 在《大逃亡》中演的角色
Hilts is Steve McQueen's character in The Great Escape.
能不能快点结束 我有点累了
Can we make this quick? I'm a little tired.
这一天太漫长了 加上你那搭档不断折腾我…
It's been a long day, with your partner assaulting me and all.
我想多了解一些 你早些时候谈到过的东西
I wanna know more about that stuff you were talking about earlier.
时代生活出版 《神秘未知》 自己看书去
Time Life, Mysteries of the Unknown.Look it up.
让我们假设 你不是个彻头彻尾的疯子
Let's pretend for the moment you're not entirely insane.
你说的那种东西究竟想做什么？
What would one of these things be doing here?
复仇的幽灵？
A vengeful spirit?
他们通常都死得很惨
Well, they're created by violent deaths.
他们回来都是有原因的 往往都不是什么好事情
And then they come back for a reason, usually a nasty one.
比如说向伤害过他们的人们复仇
Like revenge on the people that hurt them.
这些幽灵…
And these spirits…
他们有能力杀人？
they're capable of killing people?
你的手怎么了？
Where did you get that?
不知道
I don't know.
原先没有的
It wasn't there before.
你见过它了 对不对？
You've seen it, haven't you?
- 那幽灵 - 你怎么知道的？
- The spirit. - How did you know?
凯伦手上也有同样的淤痕
Because Karen had the same bruises on her wrists.
我打赌如果你去查看吉尔斯尸检的照片
I bet that if you look at Giles'autopsy photos
会看到他的手上也有同样的淤痕
he's got them too.
这事肯定跟那幽灵有关 虽然我不知道具体是什么
It's got something to do with this spirit.I don't know what.
我明白
I know.
你一定以为自己是疯了
You think you're going crazy.
但现在不是抒发体验的时候
Well, let's skip that part, shall we?
因为最近两个看到这东西的人
Because the last two people who saw this thing…
都很快死了
died pretty soon after.
你听到我说什么了吗？
You hear me?
你觉得我会死
You think I'm gonna die?
你必须去找萨姆 他会帮你的
You need to go to Sam.He'll help.
你要出卖你弟弟
You're giving your brother up?
去黄页上的第一家汽车旅馆
Go to the first motel in the yellow pages.
找一个叫吉姆·罗克福德的人
Look for Jim Rockford.
那就是我们在走散时 找到彼此的办法
It's how we find each other when we separate.
你可以逮捕他
You can arrest him if you want.
也可以让他救你的命
Or you can let him save your life.
这些是在她出现才有的？
These showed up after you saw it?
我想是的
Yeah, I guess.
好吧
All right.
你得告诉我你看到的每一个细节
You're gonna have to tell me exactly what you saw.
我一定是疯了
You know, I must be losing my mind.
你是个通缉犯 我应该逮捕你的
You're a fugitive.I should be arresting you.
好吧 知道吗？
All right, well, you know what?
你可以在活下来后再逮捕我
You can arrest me later.After you live through this.
但是现在 你得告诉我 好吗？
But right now, you gotta talk to me.Okay?
好的 很好 那么那个幽灵 它长什么样的？
Okay, great.Now, the spirit, what did it look like?
她 呃
She was…
苍白如纸…
really pale.
而且她的喉咙被割断了
And her throat was cut.
她的眼睛 深红深红的
And her eyes, they were like this deep dark red.
她看起来像要告诉我什么 但她说不出来
It appeared like she was trying to talk to me, but she couldn't.
只出来… 很多血
It was just a lot of blood.
知道吗？过来
You know what? Here.
我已经查出在阿什兰街 所有已死或失踪的女孩了
I've been researching every girl who's died.or gone missing from Ashland Street.
你是怎么得到这些的？
How'd you get those?
这些都是犯罪现场的照片
Those are from crime scenes and booking photos.
你有你的工作 我也有我的本事
You have your job, I have mine.
给你 我需要你浏览一下这些 有认识的就说一声
Here, I need you to look through these, tell me if you recognize anyone.
就是她了
This is her.
我肯定
I'm sure of it.
克莱尔·贝克尔？28岁 在八九个月前失踪的
"Claire Becker, 28 years old.Disappeared about eight or nine months ago."
但是我根本不认识她
But I don't even know her.
她为什么要跟着我？
Why would she come after me?
在她死前 因为贩毒被抓过两次
Well, before her death, she was arrested twice for dealing heroin.
- 你在缉毒组工作过吗？- 是的
- You ever work Narcotics? - Yeah.
在进凶杀组前 皮特r和我是那里的
Pete and I did.Before Homicide.
- 你逮捕过她吗？- 我记得没有
- You ever bust her? - Not that I remember.
上面说最后一次有人看见 她进了阿什兰街2911号
It says she was last seen entering 2911 Ashland Street.
警察搜查过附近 但一无所获
Police searched the place, didn't find anything.
我们该去那看看 看能不能找到她的尸体
Guess we gotta check it out ourselves.See if we can find her body.
什么？
What?
撒上盐然后把她的尸体烧了
Well, we gotta salt and burn her bones.
那是唯一能让她安息的方法了
It's the only way to put her spirit to rest.
当然了
Of course it is.
那我们到底在找什么？
So, what exactly are we looking for?
找到了就知道了
I'll let you know when we find it.
萨姆
Sam.
Sam!
嘿 我在这里 什么？
Hey.Hey, I'm here.What is it?
- 出什么事了？- 克莱尔
- What happened? - Claire.
- 哪里？- 她刚才就在这
- Where? - She was here.
有攻击你吗？
Did she attack you?
没有 没有 她只是把手伸向我
No.No, she was just, like, reaching out to me.
就在窗户的那边
She was over there by the window.
过来 帮我挪开它
Hey, wait.Help me move this.
好了 我们的小小字谜
Our little mystery word.
再加上其他的字母就讲得通了
Now the extra letters make sense.
那是什么？
What is that?
鬼魂和某些尸骸会发出电磁波
Well, spirits and certain remains give off electro magnetic frequencies.
所以 如果克莱尔的尸体在这里 那东西就会显示出来？
So if Claire's body was here, that would indicate that?
对 理论上是这样
Yeah.Well, that's the theory.
没错 没错 肯定有什么东西在这里面
Yeah, yeah.There's definitely something in there.
你知道吗 这事有点儿让我头疼
You know, this is bothering me.
当然了 你是在挖一具尸体
Well, you are digging up a corpse.
不 我不是指那个 这种事 嗯 其实我们经常做
No, not that.That's pretty par for the course, actually.
那是为什么？
Then what?
只是… 我是说 我对付过的那些想复仇的恶灵
It's just…I mean, no vengeful spirit I've ever tussled with…
没有哪个恶灵是希望自己被干掉的
wanted to be wasted.
究竟为什么克莱尔要带我们找到她的遗骸？
So why would Claire lead us to her remains?
这根本讲不通
It doesn't make any sense.
好了 就是这儿 帮我一下
All right, here.Give me a hand.
她的手腕
Her wrists.
没错 跟你一样的淤伤
Yeah, they'd be bruised just like yours.
你见过这个项链？
That necklace mean something to you?
我以前见过
I've seen it before.
这种项链很少见 是在卡森大街的商店里定做的
It's rare.It was custom made over on Carson Street.
我有一条跟这一模一样
I have one just like it.
是皮特给我的
Pete gave it to me.
- 现在一切都讲得通了 - 你说什么？
- Now this all makes perfect sense. - I'm sorry?
你瞧 克莱尔不是一个要报仇的恶灵
Yeah, you see, Claire is not a vengeful spirit.
她只是一个死亡预兆
She's a death omen.
什么？
Excuse me?
克莱尔没有杀人
Claire's not killing anyone.
她只是想警告他们
She's trying to warn them.
你瞧 有些幽灵并不想报仇 他们只想找回公道
See, sometimes spirits don't want vengeance, they want justice.
这就是她为什么要带我们来这儿来
Which is why she led us here.
她想要我们知道杀她的凶手是谁
She wants us to know who her killer is.
警官 你对你搭档的了解多少？
How much do you know about your partner?
- 哦 我的天 - 什么？
- Oh, my God. - What?
大概在一年前 警察局里有一些海洛因被盗
About a year ago, some heroin went missing from lockup.
显然是个警察干的
Obviously it was a cop.
我们一直没查出是谁干的
We never found out who did it.
不管是谁 都需要找人销赃
But whoever did it would need someone to fence their product.
比如说毒品贩子
Somebody like a heroin dealer.
比如象克莱尔
Somebody like Claire.
看来我要被引渡回圣路易斯了？
So I'm being extradited to St.Louis, huh?
你擅自决定要在凌晨两点 亲自开车800英里送我过去？
And you just decided to transfer me yourself, 800 miles at 2 in the morning?
这可不是什么好事
This can't be good.
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
- 怎么了？- 皮特刚刚离开管区
- What is it? - Pete just left the precinct.
- 带着迪恩 - 什么？
- With Dean. - What?
他说要把罪犯移送到另一个地方 接着就把他带走了
He said the prisoner had to be transferred, and he just took him.
调度官用无线电呼叫过他 没有回音
Dispatch has been calling.He won't answer the radio.
- 无线电？他开走了局里的车？- 是的
- Radio? He took a county vehicle? - Yeah.
那么车上应该装有防盗定位器 你得把它打开
It should have a LoJack.You just gotta get it turned on.
这么快就要尿尿了？
Pee break? So soon?
我觉得你该去检查一下你的前列腺
You know, you might wanna get your prostate checked.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
嘿 我在车里挺舒服的 你去干你的吧
Hey, I'm cool in the van.You go do what you gotta do.
你这狂妄的贱人
You're a cocky son of a bitch.
你以为圣路易斯那些家伙会吃你那套？
You think those people in St.Louis are gonna buy that crap?
坦白告诉你吧 你活不到圣路易斯了
Here's the thing.You're not gonna make it to St.Louis.
你就要因为企图逃跑而被击毙了
You're gonna die trying to escape.
等等 等等
Wait.Wait.
让我们谈谈这事 你不是真打算做出让你后悔的事吧
Let's talk about this.You don't wanna do something you're gonna regret.
- 也许你会 - 皮特
- Or maybe you do. - Pete.
- 把枪放下 - 戴安娜？
- Put the gun down. - Diana?
你是怎么找到我的？
How'd you find me?
我已经知道克莱尔的事了
I know about Claire.
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 放下枪
- I don't know what you're talking about. - Put the gun down.
不 我不会放下的
Oh, I don't think so.
你是很快 可我肯定比你更快
You're fast.Pretty sure I'm faster.
- 你为什么要这么做？- 我什么都没干戴安娜
- Why are you doing this? - I didn't do anything, Diana.
现在说这些有点太晚了
It's a little late for that.
那不能怪我
It wasn't my fault.
克莱尔要告发我 我没有别的选择
Claire was gonna turn me in.I had no choice.
那托尼和凯伦呢？
And Tony? Karen?
他们也一样
Same thing.
托尼洗了钱 可接着他就慌了
Tony scrubbed the money.Then he got skittish…
就想要金盆洗手 我敢肯定他把一切都告诉凯伦了
and then he wanted to come clean.I'm sure he told Karen everything.
一切都乱了套 我得清理干净
It was a mess, I had to clean it up.
我只是昏了头
I just panicked.
到底还有多少人要为此而死 皮特？
How many more people are gonna die over this?
有个解决方法
There's a way out.
这个叫迪恩的小子简直是天赐良机
This Dean kid's a frigging gift.
我们可以把所有罪名都推到他身上
We can pin the whole thing on him.
怎么样？没有审讯 什么都没有
Okay? No trial, nothing
只不过又多了个死掉的人渣
just one more dead scumbag.
嘿
Hey.
没有人会起疑心的
No one will question it.
求你了 戴安娜
Diana, please…
我还是爱你的
I still love you.
谢谢 谢谢你
Thank you.Thank you.
那你为什么没给我另买一条项链 烂人？
Yeah, why don't you buy me another necklace, you ass.
别过来 别过来
Don't do it.Don't do it.
你还好吧？
You doing all right?
不太好
Not really.
那个预示死亡的克莱尔
The death omen, Claire.
- 她现在怎么样了？- 一切都结束了
- What happens to her now? - It should be over.
她应该可以安息了
She should be at rest.
那么 现在怎么办 警官？
So, what now, officer?
皮特对我坦白了罪行 他在你们俩的案子里做了手脚
Pete did confess to me, he screwed up both your cases royally.
我想 这是一个把你们的案子撤掉的好机会
I'd say there's a good chance that we can get your cases dismissed.
- 你能帮我们搞定这事？- 希望如此
- You could take care of that for us? - I hope so.
但是圣路易斯谋杀案的指控
But the St.Louis murder charges?
又另一码事了
That's another story.
我 我帮不了你
I can't help you.
除非…
Unless…
我碰巧转过身 你们就跑掉了
I just happened to turn my back, and you walked away.
我可以告诉他们嫌犯逃走了
I could tell them the suspects escaped.
- 等等 你说真的？- 是啊 她当然是认真的 萨姆
- Wait, are you sure? - Yeah, she's sure, Sam.
不 我是说 你可能会因为这事丢掉工作
No, it's just you could lose your job over something like that.
我只是想让你们俩去做该做的事
I want you guys out there doing what you do best.
相信我 这样我晚上会睡得更好
Trust me.I'll sleep better at night.
听着 你们要小心
Listen, you need to watch your back.
现在你们两个都被盯上了
They're gonna be looking for both of you now.
走吧 我得去报告了
Get out of here.I gotta radio this in.
你不会凑巧知道我的车在哪儿吧？
Hey, wouldn't happen to know where my car is by chance?
扣押在罗伯逊的停车场里
It's at the impound yard on Robertson.
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
没事 别担心
It's okay, it's all right.Don't worry.We'll…
我们会装成相关人员 这我们拿手
We'll just improvise.We're good at that.
是啊 我注意到了
Yeah, I've noticed.
- 真是个好人 - 是啊 对警察来说是的
- Nice lady. - Yeah, for a cop.
- 你觉得她眼熟吗？- 不 为什么这么问？
- Does she look familiar to you? - No, why?
我也不知道 嘿 你饿吗？
I don't know.Anyway, are you hungry?
- 不饿 - 不知道为什么
- No. - For some reason…
我想来点豆子汤
I could really go for some pea soup.